[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bones in the wrists are called by what name?", "correct_answer": "Carpals", "incorrect_answers": ["Tarsals", "Phalanges", "Metatarsals"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Snakes are deaf.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The strawberry is an accessory fruit, meaning the fleshy part is modified receptacle tissue. What term is used as a synonym for an accessory fruit?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["False fruit", "Spurious fruit", "Pseudocarp"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On the sitcom Third Rock  from the Sun, John Lithgow plays Dick Solomon. What is his occupation on Earth?", "correct_answer": "Professor of Physics", "incorrect_answers": ["Advertising writer", "Professor of Anthropology", "Unemployed"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where in the USA can you walk on a telescope?", "correct_answer": "Puerto Rico", "incorrect_answers": ["New York City", "Pasadena, California", "Guam"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did the character Enrico Pollini suffer from the medical condition narcolepsy in the move Rat Race?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is regarded as the Father of Mathematics?", "correct_answer": "Archimedes", "incorrect_answers": ["Euclid", "Ernest Rutherford", "Rene Descartes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of the ruby comes from the Latin word ruber, which means what?", "correct_answer": "Red", "incorrect_answers": ["Murder", "Bright", "Blood"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The sweet potato is commonly mistaken for this other plant, although the two are not related.", "correct_answer": "Yam", "incorrect_answers": ["Carrot", "Turnip", "Potato"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to popular urban legends, the ghost of an Indiana teen who was killed after 5 other teens pushed her into the sewer will kill anyone who doesnt do which of the following?", "correct_answer": "Repost her story on Myspace", "incorrect_answers": ["Draw a cross on 5 manhole covers", "Light a candle in her memory", "Forward her story by email"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the red supergiant that marks Orions right shoulder?", "correct_answer": "Betelgeuse", "incorrect_answers": ["Taneriss", "Bellatrix", "Regulus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This award-winning director produced and directed Gladiator (2000), Hannibal (2001) and Kingdom of Heaven (2005).", "correct_answer": "Ridley Scott", "incorrect_answers": ["Peter Jackson", "Steven Spielberg", "Clive Barker"]}]